<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Service on NikoVenag - Web and Digital Marketing</title>
    <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Service on NikoVenag - Web and Digital Marketing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 12:58:14 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nikovenag.com/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/brand-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/brand-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>BRAND GUIDELINES Creating and sending you 3 different logos that you can choose from. Your logo will be custom design for your brand and industry sector. After you choose your logo you will get delivered:
 Logo to use on your Homepage Favicon.ico WordMark ICON  On a separate pdf document you will receive Standards and best-practices on how to use your logo. Colors of the text in the logo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Writing</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/content-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/content-writing/</guid>
      <description>WEBSITE CONTENT WRITING You don&amp;rsquo;t want to write the content on your website ? I can help you with this. I can write the content for your new website. I write in 3 languages(English/Spanish/Catalan). You will have up to 2 reviews, which means you would be able to request 2 changes to the content.
We need to gather together to better understand your business and goal. Then I will make a draft content focused on the goal of your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Build Website</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/website-custom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/website-custom/</guid>
      <description>BUILDING A WEBSITE FROM A TEMPLATE Creating and building your website on your own taste. We can start from a Template and then moving around sections and navigation menu. I can change style of everything(font, color, links, etc). Another option can be that you send me a wireframe and guidelines and I built the website from there.
I can build custom wireframe and website color guidelines for you. After understanding your vision for the website and your business needs I will create and deliver a pdf file with the wireframe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Build Website</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/website-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/website-template/</guid>
      <description>CUSTOM WEBSITE You can choose a Template from the Portfolio Section on my Website. All of the Templates are fully responsive on all devices. There are different Templates that you can choose from depending on your taste. Create, Build and deliver your website in 5 Business days. This is the cheapest package that I can offer to you. By delivering you this website, you won&amp;rsquo;t have to pay expenses for Host/Infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Page Optimization</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/page-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/page-optimization/</guid>
      <description>PAGE OPTIMIZATION On Page Optimization:
 Keyword Analysis &amp;amp; Research Baseline Keyword Ranking Report XML Sitemap Robots.txt Google Webmaster Tools Setup &amp;amp; Verification Yahoo Webmaster Tools Setup &amp;amp; Verification Bing Webmaster Tools Setup &amp;amp; Verification Google Engine Submissions Google Analytic Setup Meta Tags Optimization Google Business Listing (Google Map &amp;amp; reviews) Website design optimization recommendations Website content optimization recommendations  Off-page optimization:
 Blogs posting Blog commenting Business directories  Send me an email if you need more information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media</title>
      <link>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nikovenag.com/service/feature/social-media/</guid>
      <description>SOCIAL MEDIA Offering Creation and Optimization of Social Media accounts for your Business. The basic Social Accounts creation is (Facebook Page, Twitter, LinkedIn Company Page, SlideShare Company, Youtube). I can create another social media accounts on your suggestion.
I will optimize the Title, Description, Header, Avatar, Tags and the Overall better discoverability of your Business on Internet.
Delivering of a pdf document with:
 The top 3 best tags you can use when you make publications/announcements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>